adpostjob4u.com 2018-11-15

# Privacy Policy | AdPostJob4U.COM CYBER EXPO |

## 1\. Introduction

Who we are?

Our website address is: http://adpostjob4u.com.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which AdPostJob4U.Com, (“[CYBER EXPO”)](https://www.cyberexpo.in/ "Official Websites")collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://adpostjob4u.com/ website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by AdPostJob4U.Com, (“[CYBER EXPO](https://www.cyberexpo.in/ "Official Websites")”)

The purpose of this privacy policy is to outline clearly how adpostjob4u.com (CYBER EXPO), (“us,” “we,” or “our Company”) makes use of any information that you provide when using this website (the “Site”).

We are committed to safeguarding your privacy. We created this policy to give you confidence with regards to your personal data when visiting and using the adpostjob4u.com (CYBER EXPO) website.

adpostjob4u.com (CYBER EXPO) may change this privacy policy from time to time by updating this page. We may also notify you by email of these changes, however, we strongly recommend that you review this page from time to time to stay up to date.

This policy is effective from [16th July 2013].  
This policy was last updated on [29th May 2018].

Please contact us at  **[privacy@cyberexpo.in](mailto:privacy@cyberexpo.in)**  if you have any concerns with regards to the use of your Personal Data and we will happily assist you.

## **2\. What information do we collect?**

1.  **Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, place an order, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**First name last name** and email address (via Contact page forms, New client consultation form, Email signup forms, Newsletter, Free Online Job membership, Free make money online coursed membership, Blog comment form, Offline chat contact form, Feedback/testimonial form.)

**Email address, telephone number** , Skype ID, blog or website URL. (via Contact forms, New client consultation form, Email signup forms, Blog comment form, Offline chat contact form, Feedback/testimonial form.)

**Website audience information, blog or website URL, preferences**. (via Consultation form, Blog comment form.)

**2\. Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Sites, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Demographic information such as age, sex,** plus GeoLocation, IP address, browser/device, preferences, and interests. (via Google Analytics, Live Chat feature on our website, PushCrew browser notifications, Blog comment form, Crazy Egg, Email signup forms.)

**Referral information such as website address** , industry, company, etc. (via Google Analytics, Email signup forms, Crazy Egg.)

## **3\. When we collect information from you?**

  1. Register on our site,
  2. Subscribe to our newsletter,
  3. Fill out a form or comment on the site,
  4. Applied for any type of free online Jobs or Make money online courses on our site,
  5. Make Comment,
  6. Upload Media,
  7. Fill out any Contact forms,
  8. Through Cookies,
  9. Embedded content from other websites,

**      1\. Register on our site:**

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or website URL. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

  2. **Subscribe to our newsletter:**

When you subscribe to our newsletter we will collect your first name , last name , website URL, Demographic information such as age, sex, plus GeoLocation, IP address, browser/device, preferences, and interests. (via Google Analytics, Live Chat feature on our website, PushCrew browser notifications, Blog comment form, Crazy Egg, Email signup forms.)

  3. **Fill out a form or comment on the site:**

When you Fill out any form in our websites, we will collect your first name , last name , website URL, Demographic information such as age, sex, plus GeoLocation, IP address, browser/device, preferences, and interests. (via Google Analytics, Live Chat feature on our website, PushCrew browser notifications, Blog comment form, Crazy Egg, Email signup forms.)

  4. **Applied for any type of free online Jobs or Make money online courses on our site:**

Please note for applying any type of free online jobs or Free make money online courses we may asked your name, email address, address, city , State , country and phone number. We will offer you a application form for this reason. However if you don’t want to share those information we request you to don’t applied for any free online jobs or Free make money online courses.

  5. **Make Comment:**

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

  6. **Upload Media:**

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

  7. **Fill out any Contact forms:**

When you Fill out any contact form in our websites, we will collect your first name , last name , website URL, Demographic information such as age, sex, plus GeoLocation, IP address, browser/device, preferences, and interests. (via Google Analytics, Live Chat feature on our website, PushCrew browser notifications, Blog comment form, Crazy Egg, Email signup forms.)

  8. **Cookies:**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. The user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

  9. **Embedded content from other websites:**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## **How long we retain your data?**

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

### **What rights you have over your data?**

If you have an account on this site or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

Note: if You Subscribe to our websites before 25th May 2018, Then no need to send us this request. All the data was already deleted by our admin.

### **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience : (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve our website : (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To improve customer service : (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To send periodic emails: The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

Your address may be used to send you letters, welcome kits for an online course and any other mailing communication.

### **Where we send your data?**

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

Your contact information may be sent to third party email marketing service provider.

Additional information may be sent to third party email marketing service provider.

## **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

## **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### **Google Adsense:**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non-personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

**Changes to this privacy policy:**

AdPostJob4U.Com, (“[CYBER EXPO](https://www.cyberexpo.in/ "Official Websites")”)  has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms:**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Third party links:**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only:**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions:**

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.adpostjob4u.com/about-cyber-expo/tos/) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://adpostjob4u.com

**Third-party tracking:**

**Refund Policy:**

We want you to be satisfied with any product, service or Jobs you buy or Register from us, period. We generally don’t offer refunds for our products and services once you have made the payment and elected to continue with the product.

Please note that by purchasing the product or service, you agree to the terms of the Refund Policy.

### Industry regulatory disclosure requirements

If you are a member of a regulated industry, or if you are subject to additional privacy laws, you may be required to disclose that information here.

## Akismet

We collect information about visitors who comment on Sites that use our Akismet anti-spam service. The information we collect depends on how the User sets up Akismet for the Site, but typically includes the commenter’s IP address, user agent, referrer, and Site URL (along with other information directly provided by the commenter such as their name, username, email address, and the comment itself).

**Contacting us:**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site or our Refund Policy, please feel free to contact us on-

AdPostJob4U.Com, (“[CYBER EXPO](https://www.cyberexpo.in/ "Official Websites")”)

http://.adpostjob4u.com/

City KRISHNAGAR

district – NADIA

WEST BENGAL

INDIA

Administrator Contact Person-  **Mr. Anirban K (CEO)**

Email Address- privacy@cyberexpo.in / cyberexpoindia@gmail.com

**This document was last updated on:   29 May 2018**
